

Contact

- A Cairo, Egypt
- **1** +20 112 4269 532
- ahmed.m.moneem@gmail.com
- https://ahmedmohamed26.github.io/
- https://github.com/ahmedmohamed2 6
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/iahmedm ohamed/
- f https://www.facebook.com/iAhmmed Mohamed
- https://twitter.com/Ahmedmoohamed 26
- https://www.instagram.com/ahmed.m. moneem/

Skills

- Angular +7
- React js
- Rxis
- Redux
- Node Js (basics)
- Flutter
- ionic 4
- Type Script
- Javascript
- Json
- GulpJS
- Git
- scss
- Bootstrap 4
- PugJS
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Jquery
- XD

AHMED MOHAMED ABDEL MONEIM

FRONT END DEVELOPER

About

Hi, i'am Ahmed Mohamed an energetic and enthusiastic frontend web developer eager to learn new technologies and

build amazing stuff.I'm 27 years old ,up I am enjoying building

elegant and professional web pages in a modern way. I have developed my skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Angular, Reactjs

Nodejs and other skills to help me fulfill high qualifications and

Finished Military Service in Mar 2017.

Experience

EL-DOKAN SOFTWARE

Front end developer | 03/2021 - Present

- •Create projects with angular +7 or Reactjs
- ·Work on projects related to e-commerce
- •Responsibility For Restful APIs
- Performance And Usability Testing
- •Convert PSD | | ProtoType To PugJS & SCSS

PROEMCS

Front end developer | 05/2019 - 02/2021

- •Create projects with angular +7 or Reactis or ionic 4
- ·Work on projects related to medical field
- •Responsibility For Restful APIs
- Performance And Usability Testing
- •Convert PSD | | ProtoType To Pug|S & SCSS

VALUX

Front end developer | 01/2018 - 04/2019

- •Create projects with angular +7 or Reactis or ionic 4
- •Responsibility For Restful APIs
- Performance And Usability Testing
- •Convert PSD | | ProtoType To PugJS & SCSS

Education

2011 - 2015

Cairo Higher institutes

i'm a graduted system and information with Bachelor degree , Mokattam I've Learning In Cairo Higher institutes HTML, FrontPage, Economic, Marketing,

Feasibility Study, Information Security, Network Security